Michelle Clark: Hello?
Michelle Clark: This is the AI Culture Language Explorer, where it specifically looks at how accurately can an AI Translate.
Michelle Clark: Chinese characters and still keep the culture. So this here is the repository, and it has the README, it has
Michelle Clark: everything sectioned off into public with all the datas and all the visualization right here, the actual website itself.
Michelle Clark: is…
Michelle Clark: Here.
Michelle Clark: And so, what… people can do is that they can explore the images, explore what different AI
Michelle Clark: chatbots have. They have
Michelle Clark: Interactions with exploring the datasets, and there's two different datasets based off of basic idioms or a spatial view, which is here.
Michelle Clark: And then… Different revisions can be based off of.
Michelle Clark: actual analysis of AI model responses with human responses.
Michelle Clark: And it is supposed to focus on the, SDG16, which is.
Michelle Clark: Inclusive societies, so this should help.
Michelle Clark: Interact.
Michelle Clark: give different cultures interactivity within each other. Especially when it comes to translations across barriers, and so this specific project itself is called Culture and AI.
Michelle Clark: Thank you.